Huang,
don't.
Where are you going?
Where is the USB drive?
I don't have it.
What are you doing?
Weiwei,
leave me and run!
You know each other?
Huang Xinze.
Don't touch her.
I'm telling you...
Take them away.
Don't
move.
Do you know this is illegal?
Wait.
Take them away.
Slow down.
Cute, right?
Matches your clothes.
They're our sister company.
I really envy you.
Envy me
for what?
That your parents are so open-minded,
unlike my stubborn mom.
Now I get scared whenever she calls.
If it weren't for work,
I'd put my phone on Do Not Disturb.
Hearing your situation,
I thought of a solution today.
What solution?
If it works,
I'll buy you milk tea for a week.
How about that?
Milk tea isn't enough.
Call me bro.
You're taking advantage of me, aren't you?
I found her a volunteer job
at the welfare home.
Welfare home?
To the welfare home?
What's wrong?
Hurry back to the apartment to meet me.
Something happened to Fang Wei.
Let's go.
Right now.
Hello, Prosecutor Qiao.
Something might have happened to Fang Wei.
Go down.
What happened to Wei?
Wei might be in danger.
But I've already notified Captain Zheng.
Hello, ma'am.
Yishan,
Wei was just taking her uncle
to turn himself in.
It seems
to be about some flash drive.
Her uncle ran away.
Wei went after him.
I...
Please don't panic.
I understand the situation.
Just wait at home.
Don't go anywhere.
Take it easy.
Huang,
I was wrong.
Stop hitting me.
You've got some nerve,
daring to trick me.
I was wrong.
You sent a location to the suburbs.
This thing is so light,
it must be fake too.
It's fake.
You big liar.
I was wrong,
Huang.
Where is the flash drive?
I don't
know where it is either.
Did you drop it
when you caught me?
Keep making
things up.
Huang,
stop hitting me.
Keep making things up.
I was wrong.
Stop hitting me, Huang.
Let go.
Huang,
stop hitting me.
I was wrong.
Let's be honest, okay?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Huang Xinze.
I'm telling you,
you can't get away.
Weiwei,
how can you
talk to Huang like that?
Huang.
The little girl doesn't know any better.
This has nothing to do with her.
Don't hold it against her, Huang.
You're that prosecutor, right?
Your niece?
No, no.
You kidnapped us in the residential area.
There are surveillance cameras
everywhere outside now.
The police will be here soon.
I advise you to stop while you can.
Stop?
She's advising us to stop.
We've done so much,
and you're telling me to stop?
Are you kidding me?
Stop hitting me.
Huang,
I was wrong.
Where is the flash drive?
Tell me right now,
or I'll kill you.
If you push me,
I'll do anything.
Huang,
I really don't know
where the flash drive is.
Stop hitting him.
Stop hitting me.
I'll ask you one last time.
Still not talking?
I'll talk.
Zhang Qing,
don't say it.
He wouldn't dare do anything to us.
Still acting tough, huh?
I'm telling you,
you're a woman,
so I won't hit you.
Why are you hitting me?
Then I'll kill you first.
No, no, no,
Huang.
I'll talk.
I'll tell you where the flash drive is.
Keep talking.
I'll take you to get it.
Are you fooling me?
Learn how to trick people from our team,
will you?
Call someone
to bring it over.
Only one person can come.
Try calling the cops
and see what happens.
Hello?
Are you busy?
I'm at home.
What's wrong?
Do you need something this late?
Do you remember my USB drive?
Yes, I do.
What about it?
Get to the point.
Stop stalling.
I need it urgently.
Can you bring it over?
I'll send you the address in a bit.
Come alone.
It's urgent.
Got it.
Send me the address.
Captain Zheng,
This area is wide open
with a clear view.
If too many of us go,
we'll easily be spotted,
putting Fang Wei in danger.
Prosecutor Xu,
how many people do you think they have?
I'm not sure.
But judging from the call,
there are quite a few.
We need to think of a plan.
They've already demanded
that I go alone.
You can't go.
You're still sick.
I'm the only guy
in the whole office.
Let me go.
You're not going anywhere.
Didn't you hear
them call her 'sister'?
If anyone's going,
it should be me.
You can't go.
Why can't I?
Calm down, you two.
I spent a year on exchange
in the police force
and have some
criminal investigation experience.
Let me go.
For the rest,
we'll listen to Captain Zheng.
Glad you're sensible.
I brought the stuff to you.
Let him go,
and I'll be your hostage.
Dealing with two people
is too much trouble.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Fine.
Then I'll kill him
so I don't have to take an extra person.
You're dreaming.
I'm not letting him go.
You're even afraid of a woman.
How can you achieve anything?
No wonder Cui Xiangqin and Cheng Jia
played you for a fool.
Their fund accounts are completely clean.
You're just a scapegoat.
Don't you feel wronged?
Women.
None of you women are any good.
Mr. Huang
Huang
Stop it! Stop!
A woman ruined you.
Why are you hitting me?
You feel wronged?
I'm more wronged than you are!
Stop it, Huang Xinze!
I'm a prosecutor.
I know how to resolve this.
Women.
I will never trust women again.
The money I worked my whole life for
was taken by two women.
Do you know what's in that flash drive?
It's money.
Money!
All of Mingjinbao's money is in there.
That's over a billion.
A billion!
I only got 300,000.
Women
are so vicious.
She secretly took all my money
and wanted to leave it to her daughter.
In her dreams!
How do you know this money
was left for her daughter?
Of course I know.
Cui Xiangqin kept clamoring
to break up the partnership.
Then she suddenly died.
And the flash drive disappeared.
I knew things weren't that simple.
Right?
Isn't it?
Sure enough,
her daughter had the flash drive.
Do you have proof?
You've been in control
of Mingjinbao's account funds.
Control
my ass.
You were right about one thing.
I'm just a scapegoat.
She secretly changed the encryption key
and linked Mingjinbao's crypto wallet
to her own name.
If that's not proof, what is?
Boss,
someone's coming.
Go check
if they're alone.
Follow me.
Wei!
I brought the stuff.
Who are you?
Thanks for your trouble.
Never mind who we are.
Just hand it over.
Is she alone?
Bring it here.
Let them go first.
Use your brain.
Look who's in charge here.
You got what you wanted.
Let them go.
How do I know if this is real?
Zhang Qing,
see if this is the one you got.
Yes, yes.
This is it.
You're not lying to me this time, are you?
Huang,
look at the situation.
How could I dare lie to you?
Boss.
Let's go.
We've got the stuff.
Let's leave before anything else happens.
Women,
you women
are so despicable.
Weiwei.
Police!
Freeze and get down!
Get down!
Uncle!
Weiwei.
You finally
called me uncle.
Put it down!
Don't move!
Weiwei.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
This little scratch is nothing.
You see,
I was
so brave back there.
I beat the crap out of them.
They got way more injuries
than I did.
Alright,
give it a rest.
You're still joking around in this state.
Let me tell you,
this injury...
What do you mean?
Weiwei
called
me
uncle.
Really?
Of course.
What happened?
Tell me.
That day
at the scene,
my actions
moved her to tears.
She said
she feels safe
with me around.
She also
called me her big hero.
She forgave me.
She...
Did she really say that?
Weiwei said all that?
I never said those things.
Just admit it.
What's there to be shy about?
Weiwei,
you and your uncle...
It's all in the past.
Let's not talk about it.
When your uncle is discharged,
let's go have a nice meal.
No, sis.
Why eat out?
You know my cooking skills.
I have to cook something delicious
myself,
so Weiwei
can taste my cooking.
Give me a break.
In your condition,
just focus on recovering.
The police will question you
in a few days.
Don't hide anything,
got it?
My case isn't closed yet.
I'm heading back to work in a bit.
Mom.
Call me if you need anything.
Keep an eye on him.
Don't let him run off.
Let's go.
Based on the current clues,
Cui Xiangqin's death
should be a self-directed scam.
She wanted to use her death
to divert everyone's attention
and transfer the stolen money
from Mingjinbao to her daughter.
I often wake up suddenly
in the middle of the night recently
and cough up a lot of bloody sputum.
Dr. Yang,
what is wrong with me?
Judging from the test report,
the situation is still not very good.
Director Cui,
the current medical treatment
has a relatively limited effect
on relieving the symptoms.
Just tell me.
I can take it.
Well...
I'll prepare
a few more treatment plans for you first
to see if we can suppress
the cause of the disease.
But...
To be honest,
I'm really not completely sure.
So,
do you want to find
a few more doctors to take a look?
Then...
What if I go abroad for this disease?
Will they have a way?
It's hard to say.
Academically,
we are all connected.
But you can give it a try.
How
did we get targeted
by the regulatory authorities?
Didn't you say our
cryptocurrency trading was very safe?
I didn't expect
the regulatory authorities
to react so quickly either.
But don't worry, Mr. Cui.
I've already handled
what needs to be handled.
It should take them some time
to find evidence.
Stop immediately.
We can't continue.
No
way.
We have such good momentum right now.
How can we just stop?
Besides,
we've already invested so much money.
What should we do?
You really care more
about money than your life.
Do you know how serious this is?
It means prison time.
Even rotting in jail won't be enough.
Fortune favors the bold.
If you don't take a gamble,
how will you know if we can make it big?
Besides,
we're talking about over a billion.
This little risk
is nothing.
Tell me,
what's your plan?
We'll work until the end of the year.
Before we leave,
let's make a big score.
There's no room for negotiation.
You know everything.
You framed Cheng Jia
to buy time,
so you could safely deliver the USB drive
containing 1.06 billion in stolen money
to your daughter.
You planned every step,
including your own death.
I had no choice.
But my daughter is different.
As a mother,
I don't think I did anything wrong.
Nothing wrong?
Was it not wrong to frame Cheng Jia
for your own death?
How many families were destroyed
by that 1.06 billion?
Are you saying you did nothing wrong?
What you did can't even
be described as a mistake.
It's inhumane
and completely crosses the line.
I just wanted my daughter
to live a happy
and carefree life.
From the moment you chose
the path of crime,
she was destined to never be carefree.
I never told my daughter anything.
She knows nothing.
The truth will come to light one day.
She will know everything.